findyourinfluence.com 2015-12-09

# Find Your Influence - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**Personal information**

Upon registration with Find Your Influence (“FYI”), you will be asked for Personal Information. Personal Information is provided by you voluntarily and includes, but is not limited to: your address, telephone number, email address, date of birth, and credit card information. Personal information also includes your communications with FYI.

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

FYI may use and disclose your Personal Information: in the course of providing services, to law enforcement, to third party service providers, to improve customer service, to improve our website, to personalize your experience, to process transactions, to the person you registered for FYI, to the person who registered you for FYI, to provide information about you to our employees and agents in order to administer any accounts, products and services provided to you by FYI, to comply with legal obligations.

**General Information**

Upon accessing Findyourinfluence.com, some general information is gathered automatically when you visit the website. Such general information, which does not identify you personally, includes type of web browser, browser language, type of operating system, domain name, internet protocol address, date and time of your request, website pages visited, and similar information.

**Use and Disclosure of General Information**

FYI may use and disclose General Information for analyzing demographics and content preferences.

**Affiliated Websites**

This policy does not apply to information collected from other websites.

**Security**

We implement security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. However, this does not guarantee that such data transmissions cannot be accessed, altered or deleted due to firewall or other security software failures.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small data files that a website you visit may save on your computer or handheld device that usually includes an anonymous unique identifier. FYI may use cookies for user authentication, keeping track of your preferences, promotional campaigns, tracking our audience size and traffic patterns, and in certain other cases. We may include small graphic images in our email messages and newsletters to determine whether the messages were opened and the links were viewed. Third-party advertisers may also create and access cookies, which will be subject to their privacy policies – we accept no responsibility or liability for the use of such third parties’ cookies.

**Policy Modifications**

Modifications to this policy will be posted on FYI’s website. Your continued use of the website after such modifications constitutes your acceptance of the modified policy. Check our website regularly to view our most recent privacy policy. Each time you use the website, the latest version of the policy will be displayed and will apply.

**Consent**

By using our site you consent to our privacy policy.

**Contact us**

**If you have questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:**  
Find Your Influence  
7333 E Doubletree Ranch Rd, D270  
Scottsdale, AZ 85258  
Info@findyourinfluence.com
